Nothing unimportant ever happens at the Plaza.
Christmas at the Plaza is a romance, tv movie film directed by Ron Oliver.
With Christmas approaching in New York City, historian Jessica is hired to create
an exhibition honoring the history of Christmas at The Plaza Hotel.
When she is paired with Nick, a handsome decorator, they wind up enjoying a host of
holiday traditions together and find themselves falling for each other.
Jessica Cooper, played by Elizabeth Henstridge.
Nick Perrelli, played by Ryan Paevey.
Reginald Brookwater, played by Bruce Davison.
Amanda Clark, played by Julia Duffy.
Cassidy, played by Karen Holness.
Dennis Park, played by David Lafontaine.
Aubrey Christina Plaza (born June 26, 1984) is an
American actress, comedian, and producer.
She began performing improv and sketch comedy at the
Upright Citizens Brigade Theatre.
After graduating from New York University Tisch School of the Arts, Plaza made her feature film debut in Mystery Team (2009) and
gained wide recognition for her role as April Ludgate on the NBC political satire sitcom Parks and Recreation (2009–2015).
In film, Plaza had a supporting role in Scott Pilgrim vs.
the World (2010) and a leading role in Safety Not Guaranteed (2012).
From 2017 to 2019, Plaza portrayed the Shadow King and Lenny Busker in the critically praised FX superhero series
Legion, and produced and starred in the 2017 black comedy films The Little Hours and Ingrid Goes West.
She also starred in the romantic comedy Happiest Season and thriller Black Bear (both 2020) as well as
produced and played the title character in the crime film Emily the Criminal (2022).
Plaza received nominations for a Primetime Emmy and a Golden Globe Award for her role as a
strait-laced lawyer in the second season of the HBO anthology series The White Lotus (2022).
Time magazine named her one of the 100 most
influential people in the world in 2023.
In 2024, she starred in Megalopolis and My Old Ass and as Rio Vidal/Death in
the Marvel Cinematic Universe miniseries Agatha All Along.
The tone is emotional.